Vida Chenoweth collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - LOC 33.2, 1982, c82/334 (Box-folder 9/5)
    Sound Recording Log and Titled Transcriptions. Collected by James and Cindy Farr. Papua New Guinea, Oro Province, Korafe.
  - LOC 33.3 (folder 1 of 2), 1967, c67/823 (Box-folder 9/6)
    Correspondence and Sound Recording Log. Correspondence from Ziska Schwimmer to Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, Oro Province, Mt. Lamington. May, 1967.
  - LOC 33.3 (folder 2 of 2) (Box-folder 9/7)
    Correspondence and Reports by Ziska Schwimmer. Ethnomusicological report. Papua New Guinea, Oro Province, Mt. Lamington.
  - LOC 34, 1983 (Box-folder 9/8)
    Sound Recording Logs. Sound Recording Logs include geographic location in which the corresponding Sound Recording was made. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province, Telefomin, Amanab, Green River, Pagei, Aitape, Vanimo.
  - LOC 34a, 1966, c84/794 (Box-folder 9/9)
    Photographs transferred to Series III. Material given to Vida Chenoweth from another ethnomusicologist. Papua New Guinea, Madang Province, Siroi.
  - LOC 34.1, 1991 (Box-folder 9/10)
    Saurman, Mary and Todd "Bamu Songs: A Collection of Songs Taped in Torobina Village, Bunigi Village, Etere Village." Papua New Guinea, Western Province, Bamu. June, 1991.
  - LOC 34.1a, 1991 (Box-folder 9/11)
    Sound Recording Log, Notes from the Diary of Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, Western Province, Bamu. 7-Jun-1991.
  - LOC 34.2a, 1991, c91/742a (Box-folder 9/12)
  - LOC 34.2b, 1991, c91/742b (Box-folder 9/13)
  - LOC 34.3, 1991, c91/744 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - LOC 34.4, 1991, c91/745 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - LOC 34.5, 1991, c91/746 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - LOC 34.6, 1991, c91/747 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - LOC 35 (folder 1 of 3), 1982-1988 (Box-folder 9/18)
    Correspondence from Margeret Hartzler to Vida Chenoweth, 7/11/81 and from Margeret Hartzler to Duane Clouse October 13, 1982. Folder includes a hand written sound log without information to corresponding sound recording. Excerpts from Chenoweth Diary. Diary excerpts June 21, 1983 - July 2, 1983. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Berik.
  - LOC 35 (folder 2 of 3), 1988 (Box-folder 9/19)
    Language Map of Indonesia. Correspondence and Excerpts from Chenoweth Diary. Diary Excerpts June 1, 1988 - July 8, 1988. Correspondence from Dr. Vida Chenoweth to Dr. Ward Kriegbaum September 7, 1988. Indonesia, Irian Jaya.
  - LOC 35 (folder 3 of 3), 1989 (Box-folder 9/20)
    DeVilbiss, Caryn " Analysis of the Sentani Music System: Irian Jaya, Indonesia." Wheaton, Illinois. Submitted to Dr. Vida Chenoweth as partial fulfillment in candidacy for the degree of Bachelor in Ethnic Music Theory. Indonesia, Irian Jaya. February 28, 1989.
  - LOC 35a, 1981 (Box-folder 9/21)
    Sound Recording Log, Ethnographic and Ethnomusicological Report and Original Article for Garland Encyclopedia of World Music by Vida Chenoweth. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Sentani.
  - LOC 35b, 1986, c87/572, r82/323 (Box-folder 9/22)
    Sound Recording Log. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Sentani.
  - LOC 35c, 1988, c88/629 (Box-folder 9/23)
    Sound Recording Log and Field Notes of Vida Chenoweth. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Sentani.
  - LOC 35d, 1988 (Box-folder 9/24)
    Excerpts from Chenoweth Diary. Excerpts from Diary June 14-July 1, 1988. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Sentani.
  - LOC 35e, 1988 (Box-folder 9/25)
    Sound Recording Log. Balinese sacred Christian music written by Nyoman Darsane. Indonesia, Bali.
  - LOC 35f, 1990 (Box-folder 9/26)
    Notes from the Diary of Vida Chenoweth. Maps of Kalimantan. Indonesia, East Kalimantan/Borneo, Tenggarong. 7-Jun-1990.
  - LOC 35g, 1990 (Box-folder 9/27)
    Sound Recording Log. Indonesia, Java, Jakarta.
  - LOC 35h, 1990, c90/720b (Box-folder 9/28)
    Sound Recording Log. Indonesia, East Kalimantan (Borneo), Mancong village, Dyak language.
  - LOC 35i (Box-folder 9/29)
    Report. "The Music of the Kenyan and the Modang in East Kalimantan, Indonesia" by Maceda, Jose (original in Oversize LOC 35i). Song transcriptions. East Kalimantan, Indonesia.
  - LOC 35j, 1985 (Box-folder 9/30)
    Sound Recording Log. Gamelan practice in Chicago. Indonesia.
  - LOC 35aa (Box-folder 9/31)
    Map of UNCEN-SIL Language Programs.
  - LOC 35cc, 1988 (Box-folder 9/32)
    Sound Recording Log. Balinese sacred Christian music. Indonesia, Bali.
  - LOC 35.1 (folder 1 of 3), 1974-1983, c74/313, c83/371 (Box-folder 9/33)
    Sound Recording Log and Correspondence. Includes translations of the sung myths. Correspondence. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Berik. January 8, 1982- December 14, 1983.
  - LOC 35.1 (folder 2 of 3), 1983 (Box-folder 10/1)
    Clouse, Duane A. " The Music of the Berik: Irian Jaya, Indonesia." Wheaton, Illinois. Submitted in fulfillment of Advanced Analysis of Ethnic Music. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Berik. December 16, 1983.
  - LOC 35.1 (folder 3 of 3), 1984 (Box-folder 10/2)
    Clouse, Duane Allen " A Comparative Study of the Structure of Berik and Sobei Music Systems In Irian, Indonesia." Wheaton, Illinois. A project submitted to the Graduate School in partial fulfillment of the requirements for the degree of Master of the Arts. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Berik Sobei. May, 1984.
  - LOC 35.2 (folder 1 of 2) (Box-folder 10/3)
    Clouse, Duane " A Comparison of Two Neighboring Music Systems in Irian Jaya." A comparison of the Berik and Sobei Music Systems. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Sobei Berik.
  - LOC 35.2 (folder 2 of 2), 1973-1984 (Box-folder 10/4)
    Correspondence and Sound Recording Log. Correspondence from Bob and Joyce Sterner to Duane Clouse April 18, 1984. Sound Recording November 24, 1973. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Sobei.
  - LOC 35.3, 1983, c83/188, c83/189, c83/340 (Box-folder 10/5)
    Sound Recording Log. Recorded by Duane Clouse. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Dani.
  - LOC 35.3a, 1986-1987, c87/595 (Box-folder 10/6)
    Sound Recording Log. Indonesia, Irian Jaya.
  - LOC 35.3b, 1980, c87/258 (Box-folder 10/7)
    Sound Recording Log. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Dani language.
  - LOC 35.3c, 1988, c88/645 (Box-folder 10/8)
    Sound Recording Log. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Jayapura Regency.
  - LOC 35.4d, 1988, c88/641 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - LOC 35.4a, 1983, c83/183 (Box-folder 10/10)
    Sound Recording Log. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Dauna Bira.
  - LOC 35.4b, 1988, c88/628 (Box-folder 10/11)
    Sound Recording Log. Recorded by Caryn DeVilbliss. Secret Flutes. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Bauzi.
  - LOC 35.4c, 1983, c83/183 (Box-folder 10/12)
    Sound Recording Log. Recorded by Duane Clouse. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Kemtuik.
  - LOC 35.4d, 1987, c87/594 (Box-folder 10/13)
    Sound Recording Log. Song Categories. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Kemtuik Nimboran Gresi.
  - LOC 35.4e, 1988, c88/647 (Box-folder 10/14)
    Sound Recording Log. Recorded by Vida Chenoweth and Duane Clouse. Indonesia, Irian Jaya.
  - LOC 35.5 (Box-folder 10/15)
    Analysis of Orya Music. Transcriptions and Analysis by Dorothy Shaler onsite checking by Duane Clouse. Accompanying sound recording was removed. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Orya.
  - LOC 35.6a, 1987-2000 (Box-folder 10/16)
    Sound Recording Log and Correspondence. Correspondence from Duane Clouse to Vida Chenoweth. Sound Recording by Phil Fields. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Orya.
  - LOC 35.6b, 1987, c87/574 (Box-folder 10/17)
    Sound Recording Log. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Orya.
  - LOC 35.6c, 1987, c87/619 (Box-folder 10/18)
    Sound Recording Log. Recorded by Phil Fields. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Orya.
  - LOC 35.6d, 1987, c87/620 (Box-folder 10/19)
    Sound Recording Log. Song Categories. Recorded by Phil Fields. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Orya.
  - LOC 35.6e (Box-folder 10/20)
    Orya music system of Irian Jaya. Notes by Vida Chenoweth. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Orya.
  - LOC 35.7, 1989 (Box-folder 10/21)
    Carpenter, Kelly M. "Senior Document in Ethnomusicology: An Analysis in Yale Music" Wheaton, Illinois. Submitted to Dr. Vida Chenoweth as partial fulfillment in Ethnic Music Theory. Indonesia, Irian Jaya. February 1989.
  - LOC 35.7a, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 11/1)
    Sound Recording Log. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Yale-Met.
  - LOC 35.7b, 1986, c87/568 (Box-folder 11/2)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Duane Clouse with Richard Steinbring. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Yale-Met.
  - LOC 35.7c, 1986, c87/569 (Box-folder 11/3)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Duane Clouse with Richard Steinbring. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Yale.
  - LOC 35.7d, 1988, c88/621 (Box-folder 11/4)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Vida Chenoweth. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Yale-Met.
  - LOC 35.7e, 1988, c99/624 (Box-folder 11/5)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Kelly Carpenter. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Yale-Met.
  - LOC 35.7f, 1988, c88/625 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - LOC 35.8 (folder 1 of 3), 1989 (Box-folder 11/7)
    Hughes, Valori E. " Wheaton College Senior Document in Ethnomusicology: An Analysis of Mairasi Music Lobo, Irian Jaya, Indonesia." Wheaton, Illinois. Submitted to Dr. Vida Chenoweth as partial fulfillment in candidacy for the degree of Bachelor in Ethnic Music Theory. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Mairasi. February 26, 1989.
  - LOC 35.8 (folder 2 of 3), 1987 (Box-folder 11/8)
    Correspondence from Lloyd Peckam to Vida Chenoweth. Correspondence heading: Mairasi Music. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Mairasi. 4 Jun, 1987.
  - LOC 35.8 (folder 3 of 3), 1988 (Box-folder 11/9)
    Batstone, Steve and Valori E. Hughes " Mairasi Music Analysis." Wheaton, Illinois. Submitted in partial fulfillment for fieldwork. Mairasi Music. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Mairasi. July 20, 1988.
  - LOC 35.8a, 1987 (Box-folder 11/10)
    Sound Recording Log. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Mairasi.
  - LOC 35.8b, 1979, c79/195 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - LOC 35.8c, 1988, c88/649 (Box-folder 11/12)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Valori Hughes. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Mairasi.
  - LOC 35.8d, 1988, c88/650 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - LOC 35.8e, 1989, c89/671 (Box-folder 11/14)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Lloyd Peckam. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Mairasi.
  - LOC 35.8f, 1988, c88/670 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - LOC 35.9, 1988, c88/668 (Box-folder 11/16)
    Senior Document Recital in Ethnomusicology. Presented by Caryn Devilbiss, Kelly Carpenter and Valori Hughes. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Mairasi, Sentani, Yale.
  - LOC 35.10, 1992 (Box-folder 11/17)
    Taylor, Julie "Melodic Grammar and Syntax of Abun Music. An Analysis of the music of the Abun language group, Sorong County, Sausapor zone, Irian Jaya, Indonesia." Wheaton College, Illinois. Submitted to Dr. Vida Chenoweth as fulfillment of course requirements for Analysis of Ethnic Musics. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Abun. December 1992.
  - LOC 35.10a, 1986 (Box-folder 11/18)
    Song Text. Sound Recording Log. Includes song text translations. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Abun.
  - LOC 35.10b, 1987, c87/611 (Box-folder 11/19)
    Song Text, Titled Transcriptions and Sound Recording Log. Collected by Keith Barry w/ Duane Clouse. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Abun.
  - LOC 35.10c, 1987, c88/631 (Box-folder 11/20)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Keith Barry. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Abun.
  - LOC 35.10d, 1988, c88/632 (Box-folder 11/21)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Duane Clouse and Vida Chenoweth. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Abun.
  - LOC 35.11, 1986-1989, c87/587 (Box-folder 11/22)
    Sound Recording Log. Michelotti, Gioia and Jean Williams " A Preliminary Analysis of Yali Song. From a Selected Corpus of the Yali People Irian Jaya, Indonesia." Wheaton, Illinois. Sound recording by Molly Hewitt and Helja Heikenen with Duane Clouse. Analysis Submitted to Dr. Vida Chenoweth as partial fulfillment of the requirements for Ethnic Music Theory 442. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Yali. December 15, 1989.
  - LOC 35.11a, 1988, c88/627 (Box-folder 11/23)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Art Clark. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Yali.
  - LOC 35.12, 1980, c87/591 (Box-folder 11/24)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Janet Bateman. Includes description of arrangements. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Lau.
  - LOC 35.13a, 1987, c87/584 (Box-folder 11/25)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Calvin Roessler. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Asmat.
  - LOC 35.13b, 1987, c87/585 (Box-folder 11/26)
  - LOC 35.13c, 1988, c88/636 (Box-folder 11/27)
  - LOC 35.14a, 1988, c88/644a (Box-folder 11/28)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by the Summer Institute of Linguistics. Indonesia, Java, Javanese.
  - LOC 35.14b, 1988, c88/644b (Box-folder 11/29)
  - LOC 35.15, 1988, c88/640 (Box-folder 11/30)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Caryn DeVilbiss. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Ngalum.
  - LOC 35.16, 1990, c90/721 (Box-folder 11/31)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Duane Clouse. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Kirikiri.
  - LOC 35.17, 1988, c89/675 (Box-folder 11/32)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Peter Baas. Indonesia, Irian Jaya, Citak.
  - LOC 36, 1983 (Box-folder 11/33)
    Schultz, Stanley Jr. " A Preliminary Investigation of the Emic Intervals of the Sursurunga Music System, New Ireland, Papua, New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Submitted by Stanley W. Schultz, Jr. to Dr. Vida Chenoweth for the course Analysis of Ethnic Music 443. Papua New Guinea, New Ireland Province, Sursurunga. February 28, 1983.
  - LOC 36a (folder 1 of 4), 1981 (Box-folder 11/34)
    Sound Recording Log. Includes descriptions of accompaniment and social context. Papua New Guinea, New Ireland Province, Sursurunga.
  - LOC 36a (folder 2 of 4), 1981, c81/084 (Box-folder 11/35)
    Report, Titled Transcriptions and Fieldwork by Vida Chenoweth. Graphic and Intervallic Analysis, Titled Transcriptions by Students of Dr. Chenoweth. Includes song categories, geographical information and text descriptions. Papua New Guinea, New Ireland Province, Sursurunga.
  - LOC 36a (folder 3 of 4), 1983 (Box-folder 12/1)
    Colgren, Ruth "A Check of the Preliminary Investigation of the Emic Intervals in the Sursurunga Music System, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Contrast of Etic and Emic intervals within the Sursunga music system. Submitted by Ruth Colgren to Dr. Vida Chenoweth for the Course Internship I and II. Papua New Guinea, National Capitol District, Sursurunga. Summer, 1983.
  - LOC 36a (folder 4 of 4), 1983 (Box-folder 12/2)
    Colgren, Ruth "The Music of the Sursurunga: New Ireland, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Submitted in fulfillment of Advanced Analysis of Ethnic Music 454. Papua New Guinea, New Ireland Province, Sursurunga. Fall, 1983.
  - LOC 36b, 1976 (Box-folder 12/3)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Don Hutchisson. Papua New Guinea, New Ireland Province, Tolai Sursurunga.
  - LOC 36c, 1976, c76/087 (Box-folder 12/4)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Don Hutchisson. Papua New Guinea, New Ireland Province, Sursurunga.
  - LOC 36aa, 1994 (Box-folder 12/5)
    Ethnographic and Ethnomusicological Report. Papua New Guinea, New Ireland Province, Sursurunga.
  - LOC 37a, 1976 (Box-folder 12/6)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Fred Duvelle. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Tolai.
  - LOC 37b, 1976, c76/082 (Box-folder 12/7)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Don Hutchisson. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Tolai.
  - LOC 37c, 1980, c80/088 (Box-folder 12/8)
    Sound Recording Log, Titled Transcriptions. Collected by Penny and Ginny Schlie. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Kara, Tolai.
  - LOC 37.1, 1986 (Box-folder 12/9)
    Jorgensen, Peter "An Analysis of Baining Music, East New Britain Province, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Submitted to Dr.Vida Chenoweth as partial fulfillment in candidacy for the degree of Master of Arts in Missions/Intercultural Studies, Ethnomusicology concentration. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Baining. December 12, 1986.
  - LOC 37.1a, 1982 (Box-folder 12/10)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Jim Parker. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Baining.
  - LOC 37.1b, 1985, c85/496 (Box-folder 12/11)
    Sound Recording Log, Chenoweth's Field Notes. Sound Recording Log includes names of composers. Field Notes June 7-June 11, 1985. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Baining.
  - LOC 37.2a, 1985, c85/500 (Box-folder 12/12)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Joel Karekses. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Baining.
  - LOC 37.2b, 1985, c85/501 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - LOC 37.3a, 1985, c85/502 (Box-folder 12/14)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Baining.
  - LOC 37.3b, 1986, c86/511 (Box-folder 12/15)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Peter Jorgensen. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Baining.
  - LOC 37.4a, 1985 1985, c85/503 (Box-folder 12/16)
    Sound Recording Log. Sound recording log includes composer's names. Collected by Susan Richardson. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Baining.
  - LOC 37.4b, 1986, c86/512 (Box-folder 12/17)
    Sound Recording Log, Titled Transcriptions. Jorgensen, Peter "A Preliminary Analysis of the Baining music system, East New Britain Province, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Sound recordings collected by Peter Jorgensen. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Baining. Feb-14-86.
  - LOC 37.5 (folder 1 of 4), 1985, c85/476, c85/477, c85/478, c85/479, c85/480 (Box-folder 12/18)
    Sound Recording Log. Includes musical instrument categories and contextual information for the Sound Recording Log. Collected by Daniel Limkeman and Lamoyne Schneider. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Kol.
  - LOC 37.5 (folder 2 of 4), 1986 (Box-folder 12/19)
    Field Notes June 10-11, 1986. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Kol.
  - LOC 37.5 (folder 3 of 4), 1986 (Box-folder 12/20)
    Shannon, Elsbeth "A Preliminary Analysis of Kol Music in East New Britain, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. 2 copies. Submitted to Dr.Vida Chenoweth as partial fulfillment in special studies. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Kol. February 14, 1986.
  - LOC 37.5 (folder 4 of 4), 1986 (Box-folder 12/21)
    Jorgensen, Peter "An Analysis of the Kol music system, East New Britain Province, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Includes titled transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Kol. July, 1986.
  - LOC 37.5a, 1986 (Box-folder 12/22)
    Chenoweth field notes. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Kol. June 10-11, 1986.
  - LOC 37.6, 1984 (Box-folder 12/23)
    Sound Recording Log. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Tanglamet.
  - LOC 38.1, 1985, c86/556 (Box-folder 12/24)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Susan Richardson and Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, East New Britain, Malu.
  - LOC 38.2, 1986 (Box-folder 12/25)
    Notes from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Mangseng. June 3-June 11, 1986.
  - LOC 38.2a (folder 1 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 12/26)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Susan Richardson. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Mangseng.
  - LOC 38.2a (folder 2 of 3), 1985 (Box-folder 12/27)
    Notes from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Report. Notes from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Report includes song categories and text transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Mangseng. June 27-July 1, 1985; June 9-June 13, 1986.
  - LOC 38.2a (folder 3 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 12/28)
    Grose, P "An Analysis of Mangseng Music, West New Britain Province, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Senior Document Recital, Paul Gordon Grose. Includes transcription of recital. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Mangseng. December 18, 1986.
  - LOC 38.2b, 1985 (Box-folder 13/1)
    Sound Recording Log. Includes composer names and song text transcriptions. Collected by Susan Richardson. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Mangseng.
  - LOC 38.2c, 1985, c85/488 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - LOC 38.3a, 1986, c86/520 (Box-folder 13/3)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Paul Grose. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Mangseng.
  - LOC 38.3b, 1986, c86/555 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - LOC 38.3c, 1986, c86/510 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - LOC 38.3d, 1986 (Box-folder 13/6)
    Notes from the diary of Vida Chenoweth. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Mangseng Kaulong Baining.
  - LOC 38.3aa, 1987 (Box-folder 13/7)
    Sound Recording Log. Senior document recital of student compositions applied to the music systems of the aforementioned language groups. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Mangseng Baining Kol Halia.
  - LOC 38.4a (folder 1 of 4), 1985, c85/481 (Box-folder 13/8)
    Sound Recording Log. Includes song titles and categories. Collected by Dan Limkeman and LaMoyne Schneider. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Kaulong.
  - LOC 38.4a (folder 2 of 4), 1985 (Box-folder 13/9)
    Field Notes. Field notes collected by LaMoyne Schneider and Daniel Limkeman. Includes song categories, song text analysis and descriptions of musical instruments. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Kaulong.
  - LOC 38.4a (folder 3 of 4), 1986 (Box-folder 13/10)
    Field Notes. Field notes, author unknown, probably Dr. Chenoweth as they continue from field notes included in LOC 38.2. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Kaulong. June 14-17, 1986.
  - LOC 38.4a (folder 4 of 4), 1986 (Box-folder 13/11)
    Saperstein, Kathy "A Preliminary Analysis of Kaulong Music, West New Britain Province, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Submitted to Dr.Vida Chenoweth as partial fulfillment in candidacy for the degree of Master of Arts. Field notes collected by LaMoyne Schneider and Daniel Limkeman. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Kaulong. February, 1986.
  - LOC 38.4b, 1985 (Box-folder 13/12)
    Sound Recording Log. Includes song titles and categories. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Kaulong.
  - LOC 38.4c, 1985, c85/483 (Box-folder 13/13)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by LaMoyne Schneider and Dan Limkeman. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Kaulong.
  - LOC 38.4d, 1985, c85/484 (Box-folder 13/14)
  - LOC 38.4e, 1985, c85/485 (Box-folder 13/15)
  - LOC 38.4f, 1985, c85/486 (Box-folder 13/16)
  - LOC 38.4g, 1986, c86/518 (Box-folder 13/17)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Kathy Saperstein. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Kaulong.
  - LOC 38.4aa, 1986 (Box-folder 13/18)
    Saperstein, Kathy "Document in Ethnomusicology, An Analysis of Kaulong Music, West New Britain Province, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Submitted to Dr. Vida Chenoweth as partial fulfillment in Candidacy for the degree of Master of Intercultural Communications. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Kaulong. December, 1986.
  - LOC 38.5, 1990 (Box-folder 13/19)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Peter Bachet. Papua New Guinea, West New Britain, Kaulong.
  - LOC 39 (folder 1 of 5) (Box-folder 13/20)
    Report. Ethnographic report, includes song categories. Papua New Guinea, Duke of York Islands.
  - LOC 39 (folder 2 of 5), 1985 (Box-folder 13/21)
    Correspondence and Report. Schneider, Lamoyne "Grammar and Syntax of the Music from the Duke of York Islands, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Papua New Guinea, Duke of York Islands. December 13, 1985.
  - LOC 39 (folder 3 of 5) (Box-folder 13/22)
    Etic Transcriptions. Student Transcriptions. Papua New Guinea, Duke of York Islands.
  - LOC 39 (folder 4 of 5), 1984 (Box-folder 13/23)
    Report. Schneider, LaMoyne "Preliminary Analysis of the Songs from The Duke of York Islands, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Papua New Guinea, Duke of York Islands. December 12, 1984.
  - LOC 39 (folder 5 of 5), 1985 (Box-folder 13/24)
    Report. Schneider, LaMoyne " Testing of Similar Etic Units in Contrast Duke of York, Papua New Guinea." Wheaton, Illinois. Papua New Guinea, Duke of York Islands. October, 1985.
  - LOC 39a, 1981 (Box-folder 13/25)
    Sound Recording Log. Collected by Dean Moore. Papua New Guinea, Duke of York Islands, Romaaina.
  - LOC 39b, 1981, c81/069 (Box-folder 13/26)
  - LOC 39c, 1981, c81/070 (Box-folder 13/27)
  - LOC 39d, 1981, c81/071 (Box-folder 13/28)
  - LOC 39e, 1982, c81/072 (Box-folder 13/29)
  - LOC 39f, 1982, c81/073 (Box-folder 13/30)